===============================================================

Privacy Policy for PrepaidCompare.net
-------------------------------------

The privacy of our visitors to _Prepaid Compare_ is important to us.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Prepaid Compare, and how we safeguard your information. First and foremost, we never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personal Information we collect**  
We do not collect any personally identifiable information from website visitors.

**Log Files**  
Our web host, Pair Networks ([privacy policy](https://www.pair.com/why-pair/hosting-policies/privacy-policy/)), and our CDN provider Cloudflare ([privacy policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/)) create log files recording visits to this site. The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. This information is used only for statistical purposes to improve the performance and usability of the site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Prepaid Compare does not use cookies or web beacons. However our CDN provider Cloudflare may set cookies in your browser to  "_maximize network resources, manage traffic, and protect our Customers’ sites from malicious traffic._" For details about the cookies Cloudflare uses see this [page](https://support.cloudflare.com/hc/en-us/articles/200170156-What-does-the-CloudFlare-cfduid-cookie-do-).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies in your browser settings, or with a browser extension such as uBlock Origin. Blocking cookies will not affect the operation of this site, however, it can affect how you are able to interact with other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Interest Based Advertising**  
We do not use interest based advertising or web trackers.
